Lim Kuang Tar

• Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia

Portfolio

% +(60)16-4230329

□ buddy.tlimk@gmail.com

in LinkedIn

SUMMARY

Web developer primarily focused on front-end development using React is with 2 years of working experience.

Experienced in developing, optimizing and maintaining an application throughout its lifecycle in an Agile software development.

Built an entirely new front-end platform for Chinapress consisting of 90+ screens in the span of 6 months.

EDUCATION

MULTIMEDIA UNIVERSITY CYBERJAYA

June 2017 - June 2020

Bachelor of Computer Science (Hons.) - specializing Game Development

WORK EXPERIENCE

REDSQUARE SOFTWARE, Software Associate / Mid Front-end Developer

May 2021 - Current

- Develop up to 3 web applications projects over the course of a year under an Agile environment
- Develop and implemented over 90+ responsive screens based on user interface design using React concepts and frameworks such as NextJS
 and Redux for an automotivate news web platform over the course of 6 months
- Train and mentor 3 junior front-end developers
- Participate in 100+ daily standups to receive tasks and coordinate with project members to acheive weekly goals
- Perform troubleshooting, debugging and performance testing to improve and optimize where a web platform load time is reduced from 15 seconds to 2 seconds

SHARED EXPERIENCE ART MACHINE LLC, Web-cum-UX Developer

March 2020 - May 2021

- Communicated with the project members to design, develop over 30+ API components and deliver features for an in-house web platform
- Solved 20+ UI/UX issues with Designer with regards to the architecture and technical feasibility of the platform
- Worked with CEO to analyze 5+ automated UI testing solutions to implement and reach development needs

ACCENTURE SOLUTIONS, Intern

March 2019 - June 2019

- Maintained reliability of technical concepts documentation in a fast-paced environment resulting in time saved for the Technical Team
- Analyzed the as-is processes from users with the Functional Team for the development of the platform to optimize workflows
- Produced an infographics video to be shown and viewed by 30,000 people in client's in-house software

TECHNICAL SKILLS AND LANGUAGES

TECHNICAL SKILLS

NextJS • React.js

• HTML

• Git / Github •

PostgresSQL • MongoDB •

Javascript

Webpack

CSS

Django

Express • Figma

Typescript

• ES6

GraphQL

Docker

Node.js

Redux

Unreal

Unity

LANGUAGES

• Fluent in English and Malay, both oral and written. Able to communicate using basic Mandarin

CERTIFICATIONS & EXTRACURRICULARS

EXTRACURRICULARS

- Event Director for Putrajaya Street Jam 2019
- Event Manager for IQI Parkour Malaysia Jam 2018
- Obstacle advisor for the first ever parkour park in Malaysia @ Johor International Youth Hub

CERTIFICATIONS

ADAPT Level 1 Parkour Coaching Certification